Step 1: click (1642, 267) [OK]\NI can see the arXiv homepage with a search box in the upper right area. The search box appears to be located at approxim
Step 2: type  [OK]\NI can see the arXiv homepage with a search box in the upper right area. The search box appears to be located at approxim
Step 3: key  [OK]\NI can see the arXiv homepage is displayed. Looking at the task history, I've already clicked on the search box (Step 1)
Step 4: find_and_click  [FAIL]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the arXiv homepage. The task history shows that I've already clicked on the search
Step 5: find_and_click  [FAIL]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the arXiv homepage. The task history shows that I've already attempted to type 'att
Step 6: find_and_click  [FAIL]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the arXiv homepage. The task history shows I've already tried clicking on the searc
Step 7: click (226, 70) [OK]\NI can see the current screen is showing Spotify's web player, not arXiv. The task history shows I've been trying to sear
Step 8: click (240, 70) [OK]\NI can see the current screen is showing Spotify's web player at open.spotify.com. The task is to search for 'attention i
Step 9: click (264, 70) [OK]\NI can see the current screen is showing Spotify's web player at open.spotify.com. The task is to search for 'attention i
Step 10: click (264, 70) [OK]\NI can see the current screen is showing Spotify's web player at open.spotify.com. The task is to search for 'attention i
Step 11: click (264, 70) [OK]\NI can see the current screen is showing Spotify's web player at open.spotify.com. The task is to search for 'attention i
Step 12: click (265, 70) [OK]\NI can see the current screen is showing Spotify's web player at open.spotify.com. The task requires me to search for 'at